<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:rssator="http://rssator.idgtechnetwork.com/rssator">
  <channel>
    <title>Networking</title>
    <description>Networking - White Papers</description>
    <link>http://www.idgtechnetwork.com/feeds/6-Networking-White_Papers.rss</link>
    <item>
      <title>Not Just Words: Enforce Your Email and Web Acceptable Usage Policies</title>
      <description>Unmanaged employee use of email and the web can subject any organization to costly risks including litigation, regulatory investigations and public embarrassment.  Download this guide and learn how to ...</description>
      <source url="http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/50054514/">IDG Connect</source>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
      <link>http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/50054514/</link>
      <guid></guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Converged Messaging Architecture: Five Key Components</title>
      <description>Advanced messaging used to come at a high price - separate message stores, duplicate databases, and increased administration. A single infrastructure for voicemail and email reduces costs by more than ...</description>
      <source url="http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/80048348/">IDG Connect</source>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
      <link>http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/80048348/</link>
      <guid></guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous Proxy: A Growing Trend in Internet Abuse</title>
      <description>Anonymous proxies are an unseen threat&amp;mdash;a student&amp;rsquo;s or employee&amp;rsquo;s backdoor to malicious or productivity-sapping sites on the Internet. With thousands of new proxy sites created each day, ...</description>
      <source url="http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/50060270/">IDG Connect</source>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
      <link>http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/50060270/</link>
      <guid></guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributed Capture Platforms: Reducing Costs, Removing Bottlenecks and Mitigating Risk</title>
      <description>This white paper explores the growing trend of remote workforces and the implications remote staff can have on business processes, while highlighting how a distributed capture strategy can help resolve issues related to these developments.</description>
      <source url="http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/source/46/40020112/?src=idgtn-46830100">IDG Connect</source>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2004 19:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/source/46/40020112/?src=idgtn-46830100</link>
      <guid>http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/source/46/40020112/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Productivity, Internet Abuse, and How to Improve One by Eliminating the Other</title>
      <description>This white paper focuses on the considerable downsides of internet abuse and how to eliminate them. Specifically, we will discuss the effect of Internet abuse on employee productivity, which is huge and ...</description>
      <source url="http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/50060175/">IDG Connect</source>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
      <link>http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/50060175/</link>
      <guid></guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Open Approach to Advanced Voice Applications for Cisco CallManager</title>
      <description>As your enterprise moves to open approach to IP telephony applications with CallManager, a next step is to expand how your business communicates, inside and out. It is these &amp;quot;next-generation&amp;quot; ...</description>
      <source url="http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/80048995/">IDG Connect</source>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
      <link>http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/80048995/</link>
      <guid></guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Breed of Data Warehouse</title>
      <description>This white paper looks at some of the key challenges organizations face in getting the most out of their enterprise data warehouses and explores a new breed of data warehouse technology that is emerging that addresses many of the implementation challenges organizations face.  The result: an effective data warehouse technology that equips enterprises to realize the true value of their data warehouse investments.</description>
      <source url="http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/source/46/50045298/?src=idgtn-46830100">IDG Connect</source>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2004 19:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/source/46/50045298/?src=idgtn-46830100</link>
      <guid>http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/source/46/50045298/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning information into a Competitive Advantage</title>
      <description>IDG and IBM invite you to join us for a live webcast on September 30th, entitled "Turning information into a Competitive Advantage."

Date: September 30, 2008
Time: 2:00 PM ET / 11:00 PM PT

Companies today are realizing that competitive advantage is harder to sustain when based solely on gains in productivity and cost efficiency. The focus is shifting to invest more in business optimization initiatives which rely on trusted information to develop new insights that deliver better business results. How can this be done efficiently in a business environment across multiple applications and processes? The answer is an Information Agenda - an innovative approach to transforming business information into a strategic asset for competitive advantage.</description>
      <source url="http://w.on24.com/r.htm?e=120110&amp;s=1&amp;k=FFF4591F9147AA35D99B2000E4CC665D&amp;partnerref=IDGTN&amp;src=idgtn-46830100">IDG</source>
      <pubDate>Mon Sep 15 12:34:56 -0400 2008</pubDate>
      <link>http://w.on24.com/r.htm?e=120110&amp;s=1&amp;k=FFF4591F9147AA35D99B2000E4CC665D&amp;partnerref=IDGTN&amp;src=idgtn-46830100</link>
      <guid>http://w.on24.com/r.htm?e=120110&amp;s=1&amp;k=FFF4591F9147AA35D99B2000E4CC665D&amp;partnerref=IDGTN</guid>
      <rssator:featured/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HP Trade-In Program</title>
      <description>HP and Market Velocity have partnered to offer participants a seamless, innovative way to make buying new HP technology more affordable and simplify the disposal of aging technology. This paper provides ...</description>
      <source url="http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/80101253/">IDG Connect</source>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
      <link>http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/80101253/</link>
      <guid></guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twisted-pair Ethernet: Copper Cabling for High Performance Networking</title>
      <description>Increased Internet data traffic has surged an unprecedented transformation in the data center infrastructure. As a result, network designers are struggling with cabling upgrade options.

Ethernet over ...</description>
      <source url="http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/80170180/">IDG Connect</source>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
      <link>http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/80170180/</link>
      <guid></guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All-in-One Internet Filtering Solution Solves Costly Problems for Easton Bell Sports</title>
      <description>After extensively evaluating a number of different web filtering solutions, Baskett and his team selected Bloxx&amp;rsquo;s internet filtering appliance as the most satisfying solution for EBS. It has helped ...</description>
      <source url="http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/50060292/">IDG Connect</source>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
      <link>http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/50060292/</link>
      <guid></guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building The Bridge to SOA: Reaping the Benefits of a SOA While Retaining the Value of Core Systems</title>
      <description>Learn How to Build a Bridge to SOA &#8211; and Retain Value of Legacy Applications.
Got custom-built legacy systems? Find out how to preserve their value and performance through modernization-done the right way in a service oriented architecture. 
</description>
      <source url="http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/source/46/80514148/?src=idgtn-46830100">IDG Connect</source>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2004 19:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/source/46/80514148/?src=idgtn-46830100</link>
      <guid>http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/source/46/80514148/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proactively Reduce Risk and Improve IT Security in Physical and Virtual Environments</title>
      <description>Learn more about the security risks and vulnerabilities faced by organizations, and the elements of a proactive security approach. Then find out how Tripwire helps organizations attain and maintain a ...</description>
      <source url="http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/80465943/">IDG Connect</source>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
      <link>http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/80465943/</link>
      <guid></guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balancing Remote Access and Security</title>
      <description>Remote access is great for productivity, giving employees access to all the tools and information they need no matter where they are. But, when it comes to security, all solutions are not created equal. ...</description>
      <source url="http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/80238962/">IDG Connect</source>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
      <link>http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/80238962/</link>
      <guid></guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business Service Management: A New Approach for Quick Wins</title>
      <description>Your Presenter: Evelyn Hubert, Forrester Research
Learn key success factors that you can apply today!

Business Service Management (BSM) provides a framework for managing your IT infrastructure from ...</description>
      <source url="http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/80451552/">IDG Connect</source>
      <pubDate></pubDate>
      <link>http://www.accelacomm.com/jlp/idgtn-46830100/0/80451552/</link>
      <guid></guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
